[
    {
        "front": "はし",
        "back": "Chopsticks",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんかんせん",
        "back": "Bullet Train",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "おりがみ",
        "back": "Japanese Paper Folding",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "いけばな",
        "back": "Art of Flower Arrangement",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "さどう",
        "back": "Japanese Traditional Tea Ceremony",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんせん",
        "back": "Hot Water Bath",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "はる",
        "back": "Spring",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつ",
        "back": "Summer",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "あき",
        "back": "Autumn",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふゆ",
        "back": "Winter",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくら",
        "back": "Cherry Blossom",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "もみじ",
        "back": "maple, red leaves of autumn",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "すしい",
        "back": "(Rice & Fish; Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "さしみ",
        "back": "(Raw Fish; Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんぷら",
        "back": "(Fried Seafood & Vegetables; Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    },
    {
        "front": "そば",
        "back": "(Buckwheat Noodles; Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Pre"
    }
]
